JUSTIN L. ACOSTA

jleopoldacosta@gmail.com l 717-715-6523 4 West Athens Ave Ardmore, PA 19003

OBJECTIVE

Full Stack Web Developer with experience in HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Javascript, Python, JQuery, NodeJS, Firebase, and MySQL. I am an intellectual, creative, and professional chameleon and have used my skills in environments from music based endeavors to web development. I thrive in the face of creative challenges and rapid deadlines.

EXPERIENCE

November 2019 - Present

Store Associate, Tired Hands Brewing, Ardmore PA

- Tracked beverage inventory and sales.
- Create stellar in person experience for brand devotees and craft beer fans.

October 2015 - July 2019

Delivery Driver, Thom's Bread, Lancaster PA

- Responsible for the packaging, transportation, and sales of product.
- Served as informal personal manager and creative problem-solver in a role that required significant accountable multi-disciplinary collaboration skills for shipment details and client interaction.

January 2018 - September 2018

Manager, Moira Records at Lazarus, Lancaster PA

- Planned, supervised, DJ'd, and provided audio mixing for special events, including concerts and private parties.
- Directly responsible for Moira's communication with the artistic community. Curated art direction as well as creating and maintaining professional relationships with all artists involved. Provided constructive feedback as well as strategic direction.
- Curated musical selection and sought out records.
- Managed all social media channels and customer/client relations.

Senior Teller, Northwest Savings Bank, Lancaster PA

- Directly responsible for cross selling and referring bank products and services while acquiring and continuing accounts in order to maximize customer relationships.
- Analyzed data in order to direct staff in effectively achieving sales. Performed as informal manager and was largely responsible for Branch exceeding loan expectations.
- Frequent internal and external correspondence involving highly confidential content.

SKILLS

Technical expertise:

- HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Javascript, JQuery, NodeJs, MySql, and Python
- Logic Pro, Ableton Live, Pro Tools, Reason, and Garage Band
- Rapid fluency with new tools and techniques

Program development and problem-solving expertise:

- Creative problem solving, design thinking, and troubleshooting
- Planning projects and managing timelines
- Performing high-level strategic thinking
- Setting and maintaining ambitious multi-year goals
- Cultivating relationships with clients and external organizations

Communication and collaboration expertise:

- Collaborating in corporate and creative environments
- Teaching and training individuals and teams
- Technical and non-technical writing and editing
- Brainstorming and providing constructive feedback
- Engaging clients with sensitivity and discretion

EDUCATION

2019 - 2020 **UPENN**, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania *Full Stack Web Developer Boot Camp*

2009 - 2010 **Peabody Conservatory of the Johns Hopkins University,** Baltimore Maryland *Pursued B.A. in Classical Guitar Performance*

REFERENCES

Nicole Sauder

Violinist, San Diego Symphony 717-380-5810 | Nsauder42@gmail.com

Ammar Zaman

Data Analyst, Eurofins 717-725-1090 I mrsuperman036@gmail.com

Laura Chanoski

Multimedia Design Specialist, Bridgetown Media 410-804-6023 I Laurakchanoski@gmail.com